Moving along.
Our next step is called the shuffle turn with a pivot.
If you remember, our turn step moved us so that we were putting the opposite shoulder in.
We started with the right shoulder in.
We moved so we had the left shoulder in.
That's important to remember in the shuffle turn.
We did a rhythm change, shuffle, turn, pivot.
There's actually 2 turns in there.
If you get a little dizzy, you can do a mambo instead.
Shuffle turn is the first part.
Keep turning into a pivot step.
7, 8.
So it's an 8 count move again.
1 and 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 1 and 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
If the turns make you a little dizzy.
1 and 2, so start your shuffle turn.
Just mambo and come back.
Shuffle turn and mambo back to the bench.
Sometimes when my students face the back of the room, they get a little mixed up because they can't see the instructor anymore.
Shuffle turn, pivot, and back to the bench.